Kyiv, Ukraine

Kyiv, Ukraine

Kyiv, Ukraine

# MARIIA ODYNSKA

Jr. Frontend Developer

### INFO

#### **ADDRESS**

Kyiv, Ukraine

#### **PHONE**

+380(63)596-89-24

#### **EMAIL**

mariody.work@gmail.com

#### DATE OF BIRTH

10.05.1998

### LINKS

Telegram: @Mari ody LinkedIn: mariody github.com/MariOdy

### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS
JavaScript, TypeScript
React.js
Next.js
Bootstrap, Material-UI
Radix
Styled Components
React Query & Redux
GIT

### LANGUAGES

English - Intermidiate Ukrainian - Native Speaker Russian - Native Speaker

#### **PROFILE**

Passionate Frontend Web Developer with more then 1,5 years of experience and a desire to learn and growth in a collaborative team environment. Specialize in the creation of functional components and complex dynamic SPA applications with a modern adaptive interface.

### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Frontend Developer, Freelance

January 2022 - Present

SMM Manger, 'Stillar' co.

May 2019 - Present

Manager, Tattoo Supply Shop Kyiv, Ukraine

March 2020 - May 2022

Administrator, 'Elma' dental clinic Kyiv, Ukraine

April 2019 - April 2020

### **EDUCATION**

#### Courses, ProgAcademy Kyiv, Ukraine

2020

HTML/CSS, JavaScript

## Bachelor's, Kyiv National University of Trade and Economics

2015-2019

Food Techologies and Engeneering of Restaurant Business

### **SOFT-SKILLS**

- Fast Learner & Multi-tasking
- · Good communication skills
- Adaptive personality